<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.radionl" name="RadioNL" version="0.0.5" provider-name="[COLOR blue][B]Blue Sun Corporation[/B][/COLOR]">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="start.py">
		<provides>audio</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension  point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="nl">Nederlandse radio streams plugin</summary>
		<description lang="nl">Luister en kijk eenvoudig naar meer dan 300(!) Nederlandse radios streams. De NL Radio plugin bevat enkel openbare radiostreams. Mist u een zender of doet een stream het niet meer? Laat het ons weten op github.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">NL Radio udbydes som det er. Vi påtager os intet ansvar for mulige (men højst usandsynlige) skader forårsaget på dit system. Vi tager heller ikke ansvar for det indhold, der kan ses ved hjælp af dette add-on eller eventuelle konsekvenser af at bruge dette add-on til at se indhold via indholdsudbydernes platforme.</disclaimer>
        	<disclaimer lang="en_GB">NL Radio Music Serviceis provided as is. We do not take any responsibility for possible (but highly unlikely) damage caused to your system. Nor do we take responsibility for the content that can be watched using this add-on or any consequences of using this add-on to watch content via the content providers&apos; platforms.</disclaimer>
        	<disclaimer lang="en_US">NL Radio is provided as is. We do not take any responsibility for possible (but highly unlikely) damage caused to your system. Nor do we take responsibility for the content that can be watched using this add-on or any consequences of using this add-on to watch content via the content providers&apos; platforms.</disclaimer>
       		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">NL Radio Music Service se proporciona tal cual. No asumimos ninguna responsabilidad por posibles (pero muy poco probables) daños causados a tu sistema. Tampoco nos hacemos responsables del contenido que se puede ver con este complemento ni de las consecuencias del uso de este complemento para ver contenido a través de las plataformas de los proveedores de contenido.</disclaimer>
        	<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">NL Radio wordt aangeleverd zoals het is. Wij aanvaarden geen enkele verantwoordelijkheid voor mogelijke (maar hoogst onwaarschijnlijke) schade aan je systeem. Evenmin nemen wij verantwoordelijkheid voor de content van de contentaanbieders die kan worden bekeken met behulp van deze add-on of eventuele gevolgen van het bekijken van deze content.</disclaimer>
        	<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">NL Radio предоставляется как есть. Мы не несем ответственности за возможные (но маловероятные) повреждения вашей системы. Мы также не несем ответственности за контент, который можно просматривать с помощью этого дополнения, или за любые последствия использования дополнения для просмотра через платформы поставщиков контента.</disclaimer>
        	<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">NL Radio tillgängliggörs i befintligt skick. Vi tar inget som helst ansvar för möjliga (men högst osannolika) skador på ditt system. Vi tar inte heller ansvar för innehållet som kan ses med detta tillägg eller konsekvenser av att använda tillägget för att se innehållet via innehållsleverantörernas plattformar.</disclaimer>
		<language>nl</language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
		<website>https://github.io/</website>
		<source>https://github.com/Son-of-Cronus/radionl/tree/main/plugin.audio.radionl/</source>
		<news>[B]Releasenotes V0.0.5 (4 September 2021)[/B]
		[COLOR orange]Gewijzigd: Full upgrade to python 3[/COLOR]
		[B]Releasenotes V0.0.4 (3 September 2021)[/B]
		[COLOR orange]Gewijzigd: Arrow Classic Rock
		Gewijzigd: BNR
		Gewijzigd: Classic NL
		Gewijzigd: Slam Juize
		Gewijzigd: Studio Brussel
		Gewijzigd: Radio 10
		Gewijzigd: Radio 538
		Gewijzigd: Radio Continu
		Gewijzigd: Radio Decibel
		Gewijzigd: Sky Radio
		Gewijzigd: Slam! FM
		Gewijzigd: Sublime FM[/COLOR]
		[B]Releasenotes V0.0.3 (26 Augustus 2021)[/B]
		[COLOR orange]Gewijzigd: Code en folder optimalisatie voor python 3 upgrade[/COLOR]
		[B]Releasenotes V0.0.2 (16 Augustus 2021)[/B]
		[COLOR orange]Gewijzigd: Radio Veronica[/COLOR]
		[B]Releasenotes V0.0.1 (27 Januari 2021)[/B]
		[COLOR green]Toegevoegd: Stenders Music Service
		Toegevoegd: IceRadio[/COLOR]
		[COLOR orange]Gewijzigd: KX Radio[/COLOR]
		[COLOR red] Verwijderd: Freakolympics[/COLOR]</news>
		<assets>
           		<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            		<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        	</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
